

# Elin Fredriksson

Front end Developer Student

Stockholm, Sweden (+46) 0761697600 · es.fredriksson@gmail.com

⇔ LinkedIn, Github

Skills

**HTML** 

**CSS** 

SASS

JavaScript

nodejs

React

**Typescript** 

PHP

MongoDB

Adobe InDesign

Adobe Illustrator

Figma

UX/UI

References

On request

Languages

Swedish

English

# **Profile**

Front end developer student with many years in the service profession and design behind me. I have now settled down and look forward to new challenges and I am convinced that my skills and positive attitude are of great benefit in all professional roles.

I am ready to use my skills and my passion to help a business move forward. I have a positive attitude, the desire and motivation to learn new programs. Goal-oriented and committed to finding solutions to problems that arise.

## **Education**

Fron End Developer, KYH, Stockholm

August 2022 — May 2024

Current, will graduate in May 2024

Digital design, HKR, Kristianstad

September 2021 - June 2022

UX/UI, grafic design, webbdesign, communication.

# Work experience

Event & resturant, Skistar, Sälen

November 2014 - April 2020

Worked with events, hotels and restaurants as well as customer service.

- Led recruitment activities and training of new employees.
- Worked well in a fast paced and fast changing environment.

#### Resturant, Vinäger, Visby

June 2018 — August 2020

Seasonal work in the summers

### Restaurant, Fjällgatan, Stockholm

May 2021

Seasonal work in the summers, currently working.